翻译：Iz      Tiogy      红豆包      小布拿拿
校对&总监：Iz
后期：斯人     时间轴：深夏桃子
更多动画  就在@欧美动漫汉化军团
《开心汉堡店》第五季第十七集
赶紧灭鼠[做对的事]
除虫害公司
*我想来点汉堡和薯条*
*I want some burgers and fries *
*这家店里就有*
*Well, there's some right here!
*你可别骗我*
*Don't you tell me no lies! *
真讲不好他们在外面表演是帮还是害我们
I can't tell if they're helping or hurting us out there,
我觉得是后者
but I think hurting.
起码我进来了
Got me in here.
你每天都来  泰迪
You're here every day, Teddy.
没错  但今天  是因为他们我才来的
True, but today, it's 'cause of them.
我觉得他们唱得很好听啊
I think they sound good!
总好过电话里等候的音乐
It's better than this stupid hold music.
你好  瑞纳尔迪医生
Oh, hi, Dr. Rinaldi!
不  不  我喜欢你电话里的等候音乐
No, no, I love your hold music.
大夫  我身上还是有皮疹
Listen, Doc, the rash is still there.
我都照你说的做了  不刮毛  不喷除臭剂
I did everything you said... no shaving, no deodorant.
是的
Yeah.
但现在两边的胳肢窝都有了
But now it's in both armpits.
红色的  片状的
It's red and flaky...
很痒  有鼓包
itchy, bumpy.
有时候还会流出浓水
Sometimes it's oozy.
我看起来就像《变蝇人》中的杰夫・高布伦
I look like Jeff Goldblum in The Fly.
琳  拜托别再描述你的皮疹了
Lin, please stop describing your rash.
我在和医生讲电话呢  鲍勃
I'm on the phone with the doctor, Bob!
我知道  大家都知道了
I know. Everyone knows.
抱歉  朋友们  这并不是
Sorry, folks. It's not...
没什么大不了的  这并不是
It's not a big deal. It's not...
那东西并不会进到食物里去
I mean, it doesn't get in the food.
别别别  你去哪儿
No, no, no, where are you going?
*你想吃汉堡和薯条*
*You want some burgers and fries! *
就说你呢  伙计
Talking to you, buddy!
-给你一个赞  -好耶
- Hey, thumbs up! - Yeah!
我得到了一个赞
I got a thumbs up!
这比进来一个顾客还要棒
That's better than a customer!
歌不错  吉恩
Cool song, Gene.
没错  你们唱得很棒
Yeah, you guys sound good.
-我听得很入迷  -那是因为你们
- I'm diggin' it. - You happen to be
遇到了吸管乐神童
in the presence of child straw prodigies.
我们很有吸赋
We're pretty straw-some.
本来是天赋  但跟吸管有关  所以是吸赋
That's awesome, but with straws? Strawsome?
我们融合了好多流派
We borrow from a lot of genres.
也许加点笛声效果更好
Maybe you guys can use a little wind?
你出门都带着那玩意儿吗
You just walk around with that thing?
我们刚才在乐队排练来着
We were at orchestra practice.
既然可以用钹[谐音  变简单]
And, hey, why make it difficult
干嘛要搞得那么复杂呢
when you can make it cymbal?
我们这是要玩双关还是玩音乐呢
Are we punnin', or are we jammin'?
伙计们  你们知道这是什么吧
Guys, you know what this is, right?
周二吗  天哪  是收垃圾日
Tuesday? Oh, my God, it's trash day.
不  我们是一个乐队
No, we're a band.
终于等到这一天了
Finally, it's happening.
等等  我们之前不是乐队吗
Wait. We weren't a band before?
以前那个只是小打小闹
before we had the "Raz,"
现在我们需要真正的乐队
But we needed the "Matazz."
你们觉得怎么样
So... what do you say?
-很好  我们组个乐队  -好吧
- Yeah! Let's do it! - Okay.
好吧  但我可不要自己拿乐器
All right, but I don't carry my own equipment.
很好  就是要这种态度
Yeah! That's the spirit!
好吧  多谢  医生
Okay, thanks, Doc.
天  她也太能聊皮疹了
Boy, can that lady talk about rashes.
她怎么说
What did she say?
皮疹也许自己会褪去
The rash'll probably go away on its own,
但我得穿背心让它透透气
but I got to wear a tank top to let it breathe.
感觉那里都化脓了
It's festering under there, I guess.
-你看看  看得到吗  -琳  拜托
- Look at it. Can you see it? - Lin, please!
我祖母以前最爱说
It's like my grandma used to say.
发烧得饿  感冒要吃
Starve a fever, feed a cold
得皮疹得穿背心透气
and air out a festering rash in a tank top.
孩子们
kids.
只能在外面大嚷大叫  还记得吗
Outside only with the loud noise, remember?
老爸  这可是乐队的噪音
Dad, this is the noise of a band.
你们组了个乐队
You guys are a band?
真有意思  乐队名字是什么
That's fun. What's your band name?
我们的乐队叫  小小调委员会
We're called The Itty Bitty Ditty Committee.
因为我们演奏的就是小调
'Cause we have little ditties.
原来是这样啊
Oh, now I get it.
大家好
All right, everyone.
这是我们小小调委员会
This is the first official band practice, slash,
首次正式排练暨午餐聚会
band lunch for The Itty Bitty Ditty Committee.
那是应该带午餐吗
Oh, we were supposed to bring slash lunch?
没人告诉我啊
I didn't get the slash memo.
彼得  我想你会喜欢
Peter, I think you'll like the changes
我给你的直笛做的改变
I made to your recorder.
我把它电子化了
Oh. I electrified it.
吹吹看
Give her a toot.
酷  我们演奏起来吧
Cool. Let's wail.
*汉堡和薯条  汉堡和薯条*
*Burger and fries, burger and fries *
好  这首歌练好了
All right, so we got that song.
这真的能叫歌吗
Is it really a song, though,
你只是在不停重复念那一句词
if you just say words over and over?
有道理  虽然大多数歌曲都是用唱的
Good point. I guess most songs are sung.
但是是这样的
But here's the thing.
我唱歌的时候  听的人感觉都不怎么
When I sing, people don't seem to really,
我该怎么形容呢
how do I, uh, put it?
对了  享受  就像她们俩一样
Oh, yeah, enjoy it. Same with these two.
这取决于你对"享受"的定义
It depends on your definition of "Enjoy."
我只是更喜欢诵唱
I just prefer chanting.
你们能唱吗
Can you guys sing?
不行  除非我不想活了
No. Not if I want to live.
如果我们认识真会唱歌的人就好了
If only we knew someone who could really sing.
我想我们认识  跟我来
I think we do. Follow me.
*她来了*
*Oh, oh, here she comes *
美国乐团霍尔与奥兹歌曲《少男杀手》
*当心男孩 她会将你摧毁 *
*Watch out boy, she'll chew you up*
*她来了*
*Oh, oh, here she comes *
*她是个少男杀手*
*She's a maneater... *
对啊  达瑞尔  电脑怪才歌手
Of course, Darryl... the computer-nerd songbird.
他就像时髦版的比尔・盖茨
He's like a funky Bill Gates.
*那女人很狂野*
*The woman is wild, oh... *
他真的很会唱歌
Wow, he can sing.
他都不会晕倒
And he hardly even fainted.
*她来了  她是个少男...*
*Oh, oh, here she comes, she's a man... *
-达瑞尔  -别搞突然袭击
- Darryl! - Aah! Don't do that!
达瑞尔  有没有想过当乐队主唱呢
Darryl, ever think about being the lead singer of a band?
每天都想
Like, only every day.
太棒了  你可以当我们乐队的主唱
Great! You can be the lead singer of our band.
你们有个乐队
You guys are a band?
你可以自己来瞧瞧
Why don't you see for yourself?
没错  我们是个乐队
So, yeah, we're a band.
伙计们  谢谢你们的邀请  但是
Guys, this is nice, but...
在午餐时间玩卡西欧键盘和吸管
Casio and straws at lunchtime?
这有点像小孩子的玩意
This is kind of kids' stuff.
我想说的是  如果我要加入一个乐队
I'm just saying, if I'm gonna join a band,
那得是真正的乐队  比如史提利丹合唱团
it's gonna be a real band, like Steely Dan.
达瑞尔  亲爱的  别等史提利丹了
Darryl, honey, don't wait around for Steely Dan.
他不会为你来的
He's not coming for you.
他不会为我们中的任何一个人而来
He's not coming for any of us.
一切皆有可能
It could happen.
就和我们唱吧
Just sing with us.
如果你知道能和这些和弦搭配的歌
If you, like, know a song that goes with these chords.
好吧  就一首  但不要《冰雪奇缘》里的
Fine. One song, but nothing from Frozen,
我可不想哭
'cause I don't want to cry.
*女孩  女孩*
*Girls, girls... *
连尼・戴斯特法诺
Hey, Lenny Destefano.
你在躲你的女友们吗
Are you hiding from one of your many girlfriends?
是的  你们唱得真不错
Yup. Hey, you guys sound good.
-你们是个乐队吗  -是的
- Are you a band? - Yes!
你们想这周六在我的生日派对上表演吗
You guys want to play my birthday party this Saturday?
-想  -酷
- Yes! - Cool.
不要太快  连尼
Not so fast, Lenny.
我们得谈谈细节
We have to go over the particulars.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我们要蛋糕的边角
We want the corner pieces of the cake,
一半的皮纳塔糖果
half of the pinata candy
以及世界范围内的永久流播出权
and ownership of the streaming and performance rights
和演出权
worldwide in perpetuity.
-我没准备皮纳塔糖果  -去买
- I'm not having a pinata. - Get a pinata.
好吧  周六见
Okay. See you guys Saturday.
天呐  我们刚刚得到了
Oh, my God! We just booked a gig
在连尼・戴斯特法诺生日派对演出的机会
at Lenny Destefano's birthday party!
那你要加入乐队了吗  达瑞尔
So, are you in the band, Darryl?
-当然要了  -太好了
- Heck, yeah, I'm in the band! - Yeah!
小小调委员会要有他们的第一场演出了
The Itty Bitty Ditty Committee just got their first giggy!
伙计们  我把我每天放学后的
You guys, I blocked out my schedule
日程全推了  好参加乐队排练
every day after school for band practice.
每一天  那练习量可很大啊
Every day? That's a lot of practice.
我们可不想到时候给人排练感太重
We don't want to sound too rehearsed.
当然要  吉恩
yeah, Gene, we do.
要达到最好的效果
We want to sound really good.
在连尼派对的演出很重要
Lenny Destefano's party is a big gig.
好吧  只要练习中间有零食时间就好
All right, fine, as long as practice includes snack breaks.
还有厕所时间  广告时间
And bathroom breaks and commercial breaks
那时我要说说我最喜欢的广告
where I describe my favorite commercials.
-嗨  蒂娜  -嗨  小吉米
- Hey, Tina. - Hey, Jimmy Jr.
想来你已经听说
I guess you heard the news
我们的小小调委员会乐队了
about the Itty Bitty Ditty Committee.
什么  我是想告诉你
Huh? I was gonna tell you
你挡着我的衣柜了
that you're standing in front of my locker.
抱歉
Oh. Sorry.
小小调委员会是什么
What's the Itty Bitty Ditty Committee?
是那种即兴表演小组吗
Is that one of those improv groups?
我的表弟现在就沉迷进去了
My cousin was kidnapped by one of them.
是我们的乐队名
That's our band name.
我们周六要在连尼・戴斯特法诺的派对上表演
We're playing Lenny Destefano's party on Saturday.
5点开始  结束时间未定
It goes from 5:00 to question mark.
开玩笑的  7点半结束
Just kidding. It ends at 7:30.
两个今日推荐汉堡来啦
Two burgers of the day.
我穿背心
I'm wearing this tank top
是因为医生的指示
'cause the doctor prescribed it for me.
琳  你不用告诉每个顾客
Lin, you don't have to say that to every customer.
怎么了  我不想大家误会
What? I don't want people to think
我是故意装性感的
I'm trying to look like a hot potato.
你胳膊下面是怎么回事
What's going on under there?
长了点毛而已
It's just a little hair.
我没刮腋毛  看
I haven't been shaving my pits. See?
我了个去
Oh, my God.
-怎么  怎么了  -就是
- Wait. Wha...? - It's just,
也太多了点吧
there's so much of it.
你多久没刮了
How long since you've stopped shaving?
也就几天  它长得太快了
A few days. It grows in really fast.
像动物毛一样
It's like animal fur.
-像数乌鸦乐队某个成员的头发  -对
- It looks like that guy's hair from Counting Crows. - Yes!
好吧  都这么开心
Okay, all right, everyone's having fun.
琼斯先生[数乌鸦乐队歌曲]就不陪了
Say good-bye to Mr. Jones.
各位  我为连尼的派对写了首歌
Guys, I wrote a song for Lenny's party.
达瑞尔  这是歌词
Darryl, here are the lyrics.
"他叫连尼
"His name is Lenny.
"不叫珍妮
"It is not Jenny.
"有次他吃了硬币  以为没人知道"
One time he ate a penny, and he thought nobody saw."
-真的吗  -挺真的
- Is that true? - True enough.
我只不过把吃硬币那人的名字
I changed the name of the guy who ate the penny
从"吉恩"改成了"连尼"  吃的是镍币
from "Gene" To "Lenny," And it was a nickel.
还有两个美分硬币  以及一块小石头
And two pennies and a tiny rock.
好了  听我指挥
All right, follow my lead.
*他叫连尼*
*His name is Lenny... *
那啥
You know what?
这个调我唱不了
This key isn't working for me.
可以试试D调或者降E吗
Can we try it in D or E flat?
-不可以  -为什么
- No can do. - Why not?
因为不知道怎么弹
'Cause no know how to do.
我只会弹这个调
I can only play in this key.
我也不知道这是哪个音
And I don't know which letter that is.
对  那样才对
Yeah, that's it.
我试试
Here. Let me see.
*他叫连尼*
*His name is Lenny... *
-我们的调是对的吗  -当然
- Are we playing in the right key? - Oh, yeah.
*有次他吃了硬币  以为没人知道*
*One time he ate a penny and he thought nobody saw...*
真糟糕
Well, that was a mess!
别再这么弹了
Let's not do that again!
是不  大家
Ever. Right guys?
好吧  都同意了
Okay, all agreed.
孩子们  乐队排练怎么样
How was band practice, kids?
-挺好  -还行
- Good. - Fine.
我觉得有点怪怪的
I thought it was kind of weird.
对吧  你们觉得怪吗
Right, guys? Didn't you think it was weird?
你是说达瑞尔弹你的键盘的时候吗
You mean when Darryl played your keyboard?
你站在一边饱受惊吓的时候吗
And you stood there looking terrified?
没错  是很怪
Yeah, that was weird.
达瑞尔弹了你的键盘  为什么
Darryl played your keyboard? Why?
你知道当你只会一个调
You know how when you only know how to play in one key,
但其他人想要不同的调
and the other people want to play in different keys,
你满脑子只有"啥叫调"  这种感受吗
and you're, like, "What's a key?"
老妈  你胳肢窝下的森林可真茂盛
Mom, your armpit forests are really filling out.
都看不到疹子了  皮肤也看不到了
You can barely see your rash anymore, or your skin,
还有你身后的世界
or anything behind you.
爸  你在吗
Dad, are you there?
在  蒂娜
Yes, Tina, I'm right here...
在腋毛后面
behind the armpit hair.
还好
Oh. Good.
我喜欢  我们终于有宠物了
I love it! We finally have pets.
我要叫他们"拉薇和卷卷"
I'm calling them "Laverne and Curly."
太晚了  我已经取了"哈里和萨利"
Too late. I already named them "Harry and Sally."
-等等  有个是男孩么  -当然
- Wait. One's a boy? - Obviously.
不是男孩  是男人
It's not a boy. It's a man!
才不是
No, it's not!
美国演员
如果有个是比利・克里斯托  我会知道的
I'd know if one was Billy Crystal.
别再关注我的胳肢窝了
Everyone leave my pits alone!
那边那个你生气的时候它也生气了
That one just got angry when you got angry.
够了
Enough!
今天是琳达掌勺
So, Linda's cooking today?
对  她觉得
Yeah, she, uh, thought she'd be more
她还是呆在后面比较好
comfortable back there today.
我要把胳肢窝藏起来
I'm hiding my pits.
我脱掉衣服以示支持
Lin, would it help if I took off my shirt
会让你觉得好过点吗
in a show of solidarity?
我也长了些奇怪的东西
I got some weird stuff going on under here.
-泰迪  不要  -也许会吧
- No. Teddy, no. - Maybe.
-我脱了  -惊喜吧
- Coming off. - Surprise!
我们是来突击检查的
As in surprise inspection.
-雨果  -嗨
- Hugo. - Hi.
-嗨  罗恩  -生意一如既往地好啊
- Hi, Ron. - I see you're busy as usual.
你爱咋咋地吧  雨果
Just do what you got to do, Hugo.
举报我"乱摆餐巾"  还是什么的
Write me up for disorganized napkins or whatever.
当然  我一定会的  鲍勃
Oh, count on it, Bob. I will.
不过先检查厨房
But let's inspect the kitchen first.
你好  雨果  嗨  罗恩
Hello, Hugo. Hi, Ron.
你好  琳达
Hi, Linda.
琳达你今天有点不一样
Linda, something is unusual about you today.
那是什么
What is that?
啥  没什么  什么都没有
What? Nothing. It's nothing.
接着
Think fast!
琳达违反了健康安全法第二十一条
Linda here is in violation of Health Code Title 21,
第一部分第八段
Section A, Paragraph eight.
"过量体毛需加以遮挡"
"Excessive body hair must be covered."
但我必须穿背心
But I need to wear a tank top.
必须  为什么
Need to? Why?
因为疹...拉什达・琼斯[美国演员]
Because of this rash... shida Jones.
超喜欢她
Uh, big fan. Oh, yeah.
她也喜欢穿背心
She likes tank tops, too.
真的  她超爱背心
She does. She loves them.
我正好带了发网
Well, I happen to have some armpit hairnets with me.
-罗恩  -给
- Ron? - Here you go.
你说真的吗
Are you kidding me?
如果你不想收到传票
If you want to avoid a citation,
就还是戴着吧
you'll keep those on.
走吧  罗恩  我们去冷藏室
Come on, Ron. Let's go down to the walk-in.
戳戳里面的食材  看会不会戳回来
Poke the produce, see what pokes back.
好极了  我看上去好可笑
Great. Now I look ridiculous.
并没有  还挺...好的
No. They look... good?
真的  很好
Yeah, very,
好像在胳膊下绑了两只刺猬
It looks like I trapped two hedgehogs under my arms.
也不是特别像啦
It doesn't... that much.
-我喜欢刺猬  -我得走了
- I love hedgehogs. - I got to go!
琳  你去哪里
Lin, where are you going?
我要剃掉腋毛
I'm shaving 'em!
琳  等等
Lin, wait.
泰迪  我一会就回
Teddy, I'll be right back.
-我得去一下  -拦住她  鲍鲍
- I got to go. - Go to her, Bobby!
-琳  不要这样  -别拦我  鲍勃
- Lin, don't do this. I'm doing it, Bob!
我要全剃掉
I'm taking it all off!
医生说剃掉腋毛
The doctor said if you shave,
只会让病情更糟
you're just gonna make it worse.
虽然我也不想这么说
I can't believe I'm saying this,
刀下留毛
but leave the hair alone.
我讨厌这些疹子  鲍鲍
I hate this rash, Bobby!
快把我变成怪物了
It's turning me into a monster!
你不是怪物  琳
You're not a monster, Lin.
你的胳肢窝的确有些怪物的特质  但是
Your armpits have monster qualities, but...
-我们会搞定的  -怎么搞定
- Look, we're gonna fix this. - How?
首先  把剃刀给我
First, you got to give me the razor.
你来剃吗
You're gonna do it?
-不  我都不想靠近它  -鲍勃
- No. I wouldn't... go near that. - Bob!
我们可能得租台修剪机了
We'd have to rent a hedge trimmer,
或者雇一个伐木工什么的
or hire, like, a lumberjack or something like that.
够了
Stop it!
琳  听好了  我们去网上搜
Lin, listen, we're gonna go on the Internet.
-然后呢  -就搜"皮疹药方"
- Yeah? - We're gonna type in "Rash remedies."
我们会看到很怕怕  很怕怕的图片
And we're gonna see some horrible, horrible images.
但我们也会得到一些建议
But we're also gonna get some help.
我爱死你了  鲍鲍
I love you so much, Bobby!
嗨  等等
Hi. Wait.
我们午餐时间有安排排练吗
Did we have practice scheduled during lunch today?
吉恩
Gene.
也许  你先坐下来吧
maybe, uh, you should sit down.
好的  我刚来就到休息时间啦
Oh, good! I got here just in time for break,
排练最爽的时候
my favorite part of practice.
谁坐谁腿上
Who's on whose lap?
吉恩  我们不带你排练
Gene, there's... there's a reason
其实是有原因的
why we were practicing without you.
因为你们需要花加倍的时间练习吗
Because you guys need twice as much practice as me?
不  因为我们在做些改变
No... It's because we're making some changes,
而你
and, uh, you are,
我们觉得我们该留下来
We thought we should be in the band,
而你不应该  抱歉
and you shouldn't be in the band. Sorry.
什么  我被踢出乐队了吗
What?! I'm out of the band?!
好吧  没我看你们怎么对付我那姐妹俩
Well, good luck getting my sisters to play without me!
对了  她们也走人了
Oh, yeah. They're out, too.
是啊  我们打算不用吸管了
Yeah. We're sort of evolving away from straws.
吉恩  鲁迪和彼得是接受过专业训练的
The thing is, Gene, Rudy and Peter are trained musicians.
而且我好像已经想出
And I kind of figured out
怎么唱你键盘那部分了
how to sing all your keyboard parts.
你不能同时唱我这部分和歌词啊
You can't sing my part and sing lyrics at the same time!
他可以吉恩  我们已经见识他的厉害了
Gene, he can. We've seen it and it's so good.
我带了个效果器  所以我只要
Yeah, I brought in a looper pedal, so I can just...
我可以和着我自己的声音唱
I can sing on top of my voice *
那是我  这也是我
That's me, this is also me... *
但这是我的乐队  我组建的
But this is my band! I started all of this!
是啊  你也是  最有趣的成员
Yeah, and you're, like, the most fun member.
是啊  是啊  我最喜欢戏剧化了
Yeah. Yeah. I'm all drama.
但事实上你真不能
But the thing is you can't actually...
-演奏  -你就会三个和弦
- play. - You only know three chords!
但那三个我练得很熟
But I know them very well!
好吧  两个很熟
Well, two of them I know very well!
另外一个我还在跟它培养感情
The other one I'm just getting acquainted with!
这对我们都不容易  吉恩
This is hard for everyone, Gene.
但主要是对我
But mostly for me!
-是啊  -的确
- Yeah. - True.
行  知道我要干什么吗
Fine! You know what I'm gonna do?
我会在连尼派对之前变得很厉害
I'm gonna get really, really good in time for Lenny's party!
离连尼派对就剩两天了  吉恩
Lenny's party's in two days, Gene.
我知道  达瑞尔
I know that, Darryl!
你们到时候会求我
You guys are gonna be begging me
听你们求我回来的
to listen to you beg me to come back!
门随时为你敞开  吉恩
The door's always open, Gene.
但是你走的时候能带上门吗
Except can you close it on your way out?
我要摔门
I will slam it!
愚蠢的安全门设计
Stupid safety door closing thing!
把你从自己乐队踢出去了啊
Oh, kicked out of your own band.
原范・海伦乐队主唱
后在一次演出中被其它成员换下
他们大卫・李・罗斯你了
They David Lee Roth'd you.
我挺高兴我们被踢出来了的
I'm glad we got kicked out.
浪费了我不少
That was starting to cut
"不去乐队排练"的时间
into my not-going-to-band-practice time.
-那时间很珍贵  -我无所谓
- And that time is precious. - I'm okay with it.
现在我可以专注于吸管独奏了
Now I can focus on my solo straw stuff.
比如喝饮料
Like drinking liquids.
各位  我们会东山再起的
Guys, we're gonna get back together.
我会在接下来48小时内
I'm just gonna become the greatest musician in the world
成为世界上最伟大的音乐家  小菜一碟
in the next 48 hours and that'll be that. Easy.
你要怎么做  吉恩  跑街上去
What are you gonna do, Gene? Go down to the crossroads,
和魔鬼做交易吗
make a deal with the devil?
差不多  我要让梅金老师教我
Almost. I'm gonna ask Ms. Merkin to teach me.
学校的音乐老师吗
The music teacher at school?
音调女王吗
The Queen of the Keys?
是的  一次高强度的集中指导
Yep! I figure one quick power sesh
应该足够让我去连尼的派对大展身手了
should get me ready for Lenny's party.
好主意  亲爱的
Great plan, honey.
可以放大蒜了  鲍勃
I'm ready for the garlic, Bob.
我不想当饭怎么还没好小姐
Not to be all Miss When Is Dinner
-但晚饭什么时候好  -晚饭到底吃啥
- but when is dinner? - And what is dinner?
你已经搅了那玩意一万年了
You've been stirring that stuff forever.
这不是晚饭
Oh, this isn't dinner.
这是治疗我腋下皮疹的独家秘方
This is a home remedy for my armpit rash.
我们在网上找到的
We found it online.
什么  早过了晚饭时间了
What?! It's well past dinnertime!
抱歉  给你家孩子弄点吃的吧
Sorry. It's just... feed your children.
好的  鲍勃  把燕麦
Okay, uh, Bob, hand me the oatmeal,
鱼油  和脱脂乳拿来
the fish oil, and the buttermilk.
不公平  你的腋窝吃的都是好东西
No fair. Why do your armpits get to eat all the fun stuff?
闻起来好奇怪
Oh, it smells really weird.
没那么糟糕
It's not that bad.
我是觉得  一点点奇怪
I mean, it's a little weird.
好吧  非常奇怪
Okay, it's really weird.
我来试试
I'm just gonna try it.
不  蒂娜  那是我的药
No! Tina! It's my medicine!
把你腋窝吃剩下的给蒂娜就好了
Just give Tina whatever your armpits don't finish.
-我饿死了  -鲍勃  定个比萨
- I'm so hungry! - Bob, order a pizza.
点个带燕麦  鱼油和脱脂乳的
Get one with oatmeal, fish oil, and buttermilk on it.
那你是想成为厉害的音乐家
So you want to become a skilled musician.
-是的  -好消息  只需要多练习
- Yes. - Well, good news, all it takes is practice...
-不  -守规矩
- No... - ...discipline...
-不  -和努力就行了
- No. - ...and hard work.
-不  -好吧  说这么多不
- No! Okay. - Hearing a lot of no's.
听着  我想变厉害只是因为
Look, I just want to get good enough
我想重回乐队
to get back into my band,
被发掘  做大做强  拍屁股走人
get discovered, make it big, throw it all away,
然后再次回归  之后的就有待发展了
get it back again, and we'll see what happens from there.
好吧  我们先打开练习册
Okay. Let's open up the workbook.
练习册  你知道你在说什么吗
Work book? Do you hear how you sound right now?!
吉恩  淡定  听听这个
Gene, settle down. Listen to this.
这歌真难听  这不是歌  是音阶
That's a terrible song. It's not a song. It's scales.
-恶心  -不恶心
- Gross. - It's not gross.
-真恶心  -它是音阶  不可能恶心
- It's gross. - It's scales. It can't be gross.
真的恶心
It's gross.
它不恶心  它是音阶
It's not gross! It's scales!
我的意思是  可以加点鼓什么的
Well, I'm just sayin', it could use drums or somethin'.
-什么  -没什么
- What? - Nothing.
-再来  -再来  来了好几个小时了都
- Again. - Again?! We've been doing this for hours!
你只弹了45秒
You've been doing it for 45 seconds.
我忍不了了
I can't take it anymore!
吉恩  伟大的音乐家不是一夜练成的
Gene, you don't become a skilled musician overnight.
但我正是想这样
But that's exactly what I have to do!
连尼・戴斯特法诺的派对就在明天
Lenny Destefano's birthday party is tomorrow!
-你要在连尼的派对表演吗  -本来要的
- You're playing Lenny Destefano's birthday party? - I was.
你可以一直练习然后预定明年
Why don't you try and book next year
或者后年的表演
or the year after that and practice until then?
然后看看能不能把我弄成你的开场嘉宾
And see if you can get me on as your opening act, would ya?
我在骗谁呢
Who am I kidding?
我永远当不了伟大的音乐家
I'm never gonna be a skilled musician.
我还是乖乖回家吧
I think I'm just gonna go home.
-给你奏个撤退曲会让你好受点吗  -随便
- Would it help if I played you out? - Maybe.
*他走的有点早  但无所谓*
*He's a-leavin' little early, but that's okay*
-*他看起来很沮丧*  -更糟了
- He seems real depressed and a... * - okay, not helping!
-什么  -更糟了
- What? - Not helping!
好吧  这歌还是半成品
All right. It was a work in progress.
我的小吉多芬回来了
There's my little Genethoven.
音乐课上的怎么样
How was your first music lesson?
学到啥了
What'd you learn?
学到了我没有当音乐家的天赋
I learned that I don't have what it takes.
你在说什么呢
What are you talkin' about?
你够自信
You've got swagger,
够闪耀  够有派头
you got flare, you got panache.
还需要什么
What else is there?
我再也回不了自己的或任何人的乐队了
I'm not getting back in my band or any band!
我没机会在现代伊兰特汽车广告里
I'm never gonna get to hear one of my songs used
听到自己的歌了  没机会了
in a Hyundai Elantra commercial! Never!
我很想给你个抱抱  亲爱的
I'd give you a hug, hon,
但我腋下的东西都会黏在你头上
but I'd get stinky pit paste all over your head.
你每次抱我的时候咋没有这种温馨提示
Why do I never get that warning?
该换药了
Time to reapply.
天呐  猛兽被你放出来了
Oh, God, you released the beast!
你不呼吸就觉得还好
It smells fine if you don't breathe.
我们得离开这儿  琳
We got to move, Lin.
这味儿会污染了这一片的
It's gonna stink up the whole place.
好吧  我们去后巷换药
All right, we're goin' out to the alley to reapply.
蒂娜  路易斯  安慰下你兄弟
Tina, Louise, comfort your brother.
好了  好了
There, there.
我知道怎么让你好点
I know what'll make you feel better.
蒂娜来挠痒痒啦
Here comes Ticklin' Tina.
胳肢  胳肢  胳肢
Tickle, tickle, tickle.
我不需要成为音乐家
I don't need to be a musician.
我连音乐都不需要
In fact, I don't need music at all.
-真的吗  -什么  -别那样看着我
- Really? - What? - Stop looking at me like that,
小键  你知道我说得是对的
Keyboard! You know I'm right!
那你想做什么
What would you do instead?
也许当个面包师
Maybe I'll be a baker.
或者做烛台的
Or a candlestick maker.
*也许当个陶艺家*
*Maybe I'll be a potter*
《欢迎回来科特》
美80年代国情景喜剧  主人公为一名老师
*或者像科特一样的老师*
*Or a teacher like Welcome Back, Kotter *
*也许我会去耍杂技  或者榨果汁*
*Maybe I'll juggle or maybe I'll juice *
"呆头鹅"
电影《壮志凌云》中角色绰号
*做个空军飞行员  当呆头鹅的朋友*
*Be a Top Gun and be friends with Goose*
*总之我确定的是*
*One thing I know for sure *
*我不需要音乐*
*I don't need music *
*我再也不需要你了*
*I don't need you anymore*
*我不需要音乐*
*I don't need music *
*我要把你逐出家门*
*I'm gonna kick you right out the door*
我
I...
不
don't
需要
need
音乐
Music
再也不需要
Anymore!
你为啥就不能识相点别来烦我呢
Why don't you take the hint and leave me alone?!
给  拿走吧  帮我处理掉它
Here! Take this thing and get rid of it for me!
你在说什么啊
What are you saying?
我再也不想听到它的声音了
I never want to see or hear from it again.
烧了它吧
Burn it.
吉恩  你会后悔的
Gene, you don't want to do that.
快拿走  我要去加州米拉玛的
Take it! I have to report to the Miramar Naval Air Station
海军航空学校报到了
in Miramar, California!
快出来  亲爱的
Come on out, sweetie.
你都在里面待了一早上了
You been in there all morning.
快出来  吉恩  我们还得营业呢
Gene, come on, we gotta open up the restaurant.
谢谢  不用了
No, thank you! I'm fine!
早餐没有你我们很寂寞
We missed you at breakfast.
我们很怀念你的香蕉笑话
We missed all your funny banana jokes.
比如你假装香蕉是你小鸡鸡的那个
That one where you pretend the banana is your penis.
-我不喜欢那个  -为啥
- Eh, don't love that one. - Why?
-太弱了  -为什么
- It's a little easy. - Why?
什么叫太弱了
What do you mean, "Easy"?
-他还讲过其它的呢  -比如说  哪一个
- He's got other ones. - Like what? Which ones?
他戴过香蕉胡子  扮过香蕉船长
He does the banana mustache, he does Captain Banana...
对哦  我知道怎么让他出来了
Oh, yeah. Ooh! I know what'll get him out.
谁想看老妈毛茸茸的咯吱窝呀
Who wants to see Mommy's big hairy pasty pits?
-没兴趣  -真是好主意  琳
- Nah. - Good idea, Lin.
得了  得了
All right, all right.
你们B队辛苦了
Nice try from the B-team.
你们下楼去吧
You guys go ahead downstairs.
该我们A队接手了
The A-team will take it from here.
吉恩  我们来了
Gene, we're coming in.
-B队  -好吧  我们走了
- B-team? - All right. We're leaving
但仅仅是因为我们得去开张了
but only because we have to open the restaurant.
-不是因为我们是B队  -当然不是
- And we're not the B team. - No, like in a good way.
不是才怪
Not in a good way.
你还在跟音乐过不去呢
So, you're, uh, still done with music, right?
-是的  -还没改变主意呢
- Yes. - You haven't changed your mind?
没  我已经下定决心了
Nope. This is what I'm doing now.
得  对了  我差点忘了
Okay. Cool. Oh! I almost forgot.
-这是什么  -你的键盘啊
- What is this? - That's your keyboard.
我们把它烧了  如你所愿
We burnt it. Just like you asked.
你想要的就是这个吧
That's what you wanted, right?
是的
Yes.
*键盘  我的小键*
*Keyboard, my keyboard*
*键盘*
*Keyboard*
*我的小键*
*my keyboard...*
我的小键  我不想你死的
Keyboard! I don't want you to be dead!
我们就知道  就知道你还放不下
We knew it! We knew you still cared!
所以我们才没烧掉你的键盘
And that's why we didn't burn your keyboard.
啥  这不是我的键盘吗
What? This isn't my keyboard?
不是  我们烧的老爸的新袜子
No. We burnt Dad's new socks.
他以为自己是谁呢
Who does he think he is?
要是真想见你的键盘
If you want to see your real keyboard,
那就穿上你的汉堡装
put on your burger suit,
把你那鸡窝头拾掇拾掇
do something about that hair,
然后跟我们来
and come with us.
来吉恩  我们一起演奏  像以前那样
Come on, Gene, let's play together, like we used to.
你负责键盘  我们负责纸杯
You play the keyboard and we'll play the cups.
像过去那样
Like old times.
我做不到  我不是真正的音乐家
No. I can't. I'm not a real musician.
但你总会是真正的...什么东西的
Well, you're definitely a real something.
也许音乐家这个词不适合你
Maybe "Musician" Just isn't the right word for you.
也许你更适合当个...音乐咖
Maybe you're a... musishy.
来嘛  吉恩  就弹一首
Come on, Gene. Just one song.
对  在那之后  如果你还是想放弃音乐
Yeah. And after that, if you're still done with music,
我们就真的把这破烂玩意给烧了
we'll really burn this sucker.
快点
Come on.
开始
There we go.
进行得还不错
This is going well.
就是这样
There you go.
看呐  他们真的说服吉恩演奏了
Look! They got Gene to play!
看来他们真的是A队呢
Wow. They really are the A-team.
*来点汉堡和薯条*
*You want some burgers and fries*
*要不要来点汉堡和薯条*
*Do you want some burgers and fries?
这家店就有哦
Well, there's some right here
*你可别骗我*
*Don't you tell me no lies*
汉堡男孩
Burger Boy!
给他们来点吸管音
Give 'em some straw!
转圈圈
Spin!
我这儿有放大器  你们需要吗
Hey, you guys want to amp things up?
接上  接上
Plug it up! Plug it in!
-啥意思  -把放大器接上啊
- What does that mean? - Plug in the amp!
哦  好咧
Oh, right! Okay.
看呐  孩子们都召集起一个快闪族了
Oh, look! The kids have a little flash mob out there!
看来要发展成一个舞会啦
This thing's turning into a dance party!
我也要去参加
I'm goin' out there.
狗狗独唱
Dog bark solo!
琳  那药好像起作用了
Lin, I think the pit paste worked.
我都看不见你的疹子了
I can't see your rash anymore.
真的诶  疹子消失了
Oh, yeah! The rash is gone!
-你可以除毛了  -对哦
- You can shave. - Yeah...
咋了  你不想除毛么
What? You don't want to shave?
我也不知道  我现在挺喜欢它们的
I don't know. I kind of like 'em now.
我的小哈里和小萨利
My little Harry and Sally.
-我是说  好吧  -腋毛诶
- I mean, great. - Armpit hair!
酷  麦当娜
Cool! Madonna...
麦当娜曾在Instagram上发布自己的腋毛照
表示  "长毛又怎样"
谢谢夸奖
Thank you!
你们来这儿干嘛
What are you guys doing here?
你们现在不应该赶去连尼的派对吗
Isn't it almost time for Lenny's party?
说来奇怪  在我们邀请你
Well, funny story. Um, after you were invited
离开乐队  你不情愿地接受以后
to leave the band, and you reluctantly accepted,
我们
we,
就不好玩了
It's not fun anymore!
你们这是来道歉了吗
So you're saying you're sorry?
对  我们想要你和我们一起
Yeah. Want to get the band back together
去连尼的派对表演
and go play Lenny's party?
好吧
All right.
谁想去一个酷炫六年级小学生的派对啊
Hey! Who wants to go to a cool sixth grader's party?
耶  让我们带大家
Yay! Let's lead everybody
离开餐馆吧
away from the restaurant!
-别别别别  -要要要要
- No, no, no, no! No, no! - Yes, yes, yes, yes!
希望连尼不介意
I hope Lenny's okay with this.
我犯什么傻呢
What am I saying?
他可是连尼・戴斯特法诺  你们会爱上他的
He's Lenny Destefano. You guys are gonna love him!
*我想来点汉堡和薯条*
*I want some burgers and fries*
*这家店就有哦*
*Well, there's some right here*
*你可别骗我*
*Don't you tell me no lies*
*我想来点汉堡和薯条*
*I want some burgers and fries*
*这家店就有哦*
*Well, there's some right here*
*你可别骗我*
*Don't you tell me no lies*
*我想来点汉堡和薯条*
*I want some burgers and fries*
*我想*
*I want... *
*这家店就有哦*
*Well, there's some right here*
*你可别骗我*
*Don't you tell me no lies*
*我想来点汉堡和薯条*
*I want some burgers and fries, ooh...*
*这家店就有哦*
*Well, there's some right here*
*你可别骗我*
*Don't you tell me no lies*